txteagle.com 2019-05-18

# Jana | Privacy Policy

## Privacy Policy

This Privacy Policy is applicable to [www.jana.com](http://www.jana.com/?hsLang=en-us) and any other site that may be operated by or for Jana Mobile, Inc. (together, the "Websites"). It explains how we collect information from users of the Websites and how we use such information. Your use of the Websites constitutes your acceptance of this Privacy Policy. Jana Mobile, Inc. understands that your online privacy is important to you. We have created the following Privacy Policy to let you know what information we collect on this website, 

Please read this privacy policy carefully. Use of this website and your sharing of information with us is subject to the terms and conditions of this Privacy Policy. By using this website or sharing information with us, you give your agreement to this Privacy Policy. The Privacy Policy may be revised or updated at any time by us as further described below.

The terms “you,” “your,” and “yours” refer to the website visitor or customer. The terms “Jana,” "Jana Mobile, Inc.," “we,” “us,” and “our” refer to Jana.

## Information We Collect

When entering information on our site, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your name, email address, mailing address or other details to help you with your experience.

### Ad Delivery & Reporting Across Multiple Sites

### Internet Technology

## How We Collect Information

We collect information from you when you subscribe to a newsletter, fill out a form, or enter information on our site. Additionally, if you're creating an account via Jana Launch (launch.jana.com), our self-service campaign manager, your information will be collected at that time. 

## How We Use Information

We may use the information we collect from you when you register, sign up for our newsletter, respond to a survey, download a white paper, sign up for a webinar,  respond to marketing communication, browse the website, or use certain other site features in the following way to send periodic emails regarding our services or products and for follow up correspondence regarding inquiries. 

## Children's Privacy

### Children’s Privacy

Jana’s products and services are neither developed for, nor directed at, children. If you believe your child has provided us with PII through the Jana corporate site or through our corporate marketing materials, please contact us and we will delete any such data.

## Security

### Security

Jana employs standard measures to ensure the security of all information. We routinely evaluate our practices to identify security threats or opportunities for the improvement of our services. No transmission of information is guaranteed to be completely secure. Unauthorized entry or use, hardware or software failure, and other factors may compromise data security. You acknowledge and agree to assume these risks when communicating with us.

### Personally Identifiable Information

## Changes

### IBA Opt-Out

### Changes

Jana may find it appropriate or necessary, or may be legally obligated, to update this Privacy Policy from time to time. When we do, we will post those changes on this page and update the effective date (found at the bottom) so that you have a way to always become aware of the information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances we disclose it. For changes to this Privacy Policy that may be materially less restrictive on our use or disclosure of information you have already provided to us, we will attempt to obtain your consent (if we have the necessary contact information) before implementing such revisions with respect to such information, or notify you either by placing a prominent notice on the home page of our website or by directly sending you a notification. For all other changes, it is your responsibility to review this Privacy Policy frequently and remain informed about any changes to it, so we encourage you to visit this page often. 

You understand and agree that Jana's liability from any dispute over privacy or this privacy policy will be limited as set forth in the terms and conditions of our applicable website terms and conditions. 

## Contact Us

If you have questions about this Privacy Policy, the practices of or your dealings with us relating to this Privacy Policy, please email us at info@jana.com or you can send correspondence to us at the following address:

Jana Mobile, Inc.  
101 Arch Street  
9th Floor  
Boston, MA 02110

Privacy Policy – January 1, 2017
